

# **YOUNGHYUN KIM**

PRODUCT DESIGNER FRONT-END WEB DEVELOPER

I'm a product designer with a strong foundation in UX/UI and front-end web development.

My expertise spans across various technologies including JavaScript, React, and modern CSS frameworks. With a keen eye for detail and a passion for creating intuitive user experiences, I bridge the gap between design and functionality.

## **LANGUAGES**

→ Korean Native

→ English Fluent

→ French Intermediate

### **CERTIFICATION**

Web Design Technician 2024 Certificate

Human Resources Development Service of South Korea

### **CONTACT**

#### **Portfolio**

https://honeyprofit.github.io/portfolio

### **Github**

https://github.com/honeyprofit

#### **Email**

honeyprofit@gmail.com

X

@YH4525402121608

### **SKILLS**

→ **Design Tools** Figma, Midjourney, Adobe

Suite (Photoshop,

Illustrator, InDesign, Premiere)

→ Development HTML, CSS, SCSS,

JavaScript, jQuery, React, React Native, Redux, Tailwind,

Node.js, Python, Java

→ Low-Code Framer, Webflow, Shopify

## **EXPERIENCE**

<b>UI/UX Designer</b> Freelancer	2022 - current
Web Designer Ubitec LTD, South Korea	2020 - 2021
<b>Web Designer</b> Kilic Fashion LTD, UK	2019 - 2020
Graphic Designer & Illustrator	2017 - 2019

### **EDUCATION**

Freelancer

UI/UX Web/App Design(Figma) & Frontend(React) Ezen Academy Gangnam DX Education Seoul, South Korea	2024 Center,
Beginners In JavaScript boostcourse	2024
CS50's Web Programming With Python And JavaScript	2023
Master Of Illustration Middlesex University, London, UK	2019 - 2020
Bachelor Of Business Administration Ewha Womans University, Seoul, South R	2005 - 2009 Korea

2004

Premiere/After Effects Video

Hongik University, Seoul, South Korea

**Editing**